hi Springs and welcome to another
嗨斯普林斯，欢迎来到另一个
installment of spring tips and listen
春季小贴士和听
summit wouldn't look at GBC yes the LBC
峰会不会看GBC是LBC
the basic driver layer the database
数据库的基本驱动程序层
connectivity the java java database kick
连接Java Java数据库踢
to delay that we can use to talk to
延迟我们可以用来与之交谈
secret based data sources and I mean
基于秘密的数据源，我的意思是
everything right as my Mexico server
一切正常，如我的墨西哥服务器
oracle post graves my sequel the sequel
甲骨文发布坟墓我的续集续集
light you know Microsoft Access I mean
您知道我的意思是Microsoft Access
Informix Sybase h2h sequel Derby
Informix Sybase H2H续集Derby
everything you can imagine ever wanting
你想像得到的一切
to talk to us in terms of a of sequel
跟我们聊续集
you can support to this obit kritis and
您可以支持这种肥胖性角膜炎，
very well known program model now while
现在非常著名的程序模型
JDBC is youthful Roth's very powerful it
JDBC是年轻的罗斯，它非常强大
is not of all the things that it is it
并不是所有的一切
is not a convenient they use and this
他们使用起来不方便，这
has been true for 20 odd years so that's
已经有20多年的历史了，所以
okay right there's a lot of ground above
好吧，上面有很多地面
it on which to to provide simplicity and
在其上提供简单性和
power and so the ecosystem has sought to
力量，因此生态系统已寻求
fill that gap and when the earliest and
填补这一空白，最早
still most diverse was almost too
仍然是最多样化的
powerful entrance to that space I think
我认为该空间的强大入口
is is spring Spring has I think some
是春天我想一些春天
support that has actually been around
实际上已经存在的支持
since the very beginning of spring it's
从春天开始
one of the earliest you know things that
您最早知道的事情之一
we did in spring was to simplify working
我们在春季所做的是简化工作
with JDBC and for a lot of people
JDBC和很多人
including myself yours truly it is one
包括我自己在内，这确实是一个
of the first thing that we saw as so the
我们看到的第一件事
you saw in spring as is representing
你在春天看到了代表
utility that we would want to to need to
我们想要的实用工具
spring a week for spring to be able to
一周的春天，以便能够
use right so JDBC is a an old topic that
使用权，因此JDBC是一个古老的话题，
there is a seemingly no end of interest
似乎没有尽头的兴趣
in it and naturally and there's a lot of
自然而然地，有很多
really useful technologies out there
真正有用的技术
that make it a powerful place to a
使其成为一个强大的地方
powerful way to build applications and
构建应用程序的强大方法
so today I'm gonna take up time and just
所以今天我要花时间
look at a number of the different things
看一些不同的东西
that are supported in basic spring and
在基本春季中得到支持
and some of the ecosystem so I'm gonna
还有一些生态系统，所以我要
build it spring the application we need
建立它，我们需要的应用程序
to talk to my sequel I've got in my
和我的续集谈谈
secret ladies running in my local
在我当地跑的秘密女士
machine here so we're using my circle
机在这里，所以我们用我的圈子
use Lombok to make a short work of
用龙目岛做一个简短的工作
cleaning so DTL entity type records
清理，以便DTL实体类型记录
today or a plate am an application that
今天或一个盘子是一个应用程序
uses the jb support and spring and
使用jb support和spring和
spring boot itself so I'm gonna bring
spring boot 本身，所以我要带
that in and that's it for now we need my
那就是现在，我们需要我的
sequel I'm using
我正在使用的续集
a few of the default check boxes here
这里的一些默认复选框
there are a few options here there's a
这里有一些选择
you know nobody whether different J
你知道没人是否不同的J
bases h2 is supported for example
例如支持bases h2
post-crisis is there as well let's see
危机后也在那里让我们看看
if Microsoft sequence over there it is
如果微软在那边排序
as well so there's a number of different
还有很多不同的
options that you could set there the box
您可以在此处设置的选项
but that is by no means the exhaustive
但这绝不是详尽的
list of things are supported by spring
春天支持的事情清单
obviously these are just a sort of
显然，这些只是一种
useful things out of the box let's go
开箱即用的有用的东西，让我们开始吧
ahead and throw the Downloads directory
向前并抛出Downloads目录
here I think I already have a duplicate
在这里我想我已经有一个副本
directory so goodbye to all that yes
目录再见了
good take to generate and there's my a
产生的好机会，还有我的
zip file so it would open it up in my
zip文件，以便将其打开
IDE and we can go ahead and go to some
IDE，我们可以继续
publication that talks to to my sequel
与我的续集有关的出版物
now again I've got that in my local
现在再次在本地
machine that's running under the host
在主机下运行的计算机
serum which is running on my local
在我本地运行的血清
machine and so my sequel you see RM h h
机器，所以我的续集，你看到RM hh
is equal to CM p and then serum p is the
等于CM p，然后血清p是
requires me to send a password right so
要求我正确发送密码，以便
if i do that i am gonna show tables drop
如果我这样做，我将显示表格下降
table customers drop table orders
表客户放弃表订单
alright so there we are
好了，我们在那里
so show tables nothing left now we're
所以显示表，现在我们什么都没有了
gonna build an application that can talk
将建立一个可以交谈的应用程序
to my database and in order to do this i
到我的数据库，为了做到这一点，我
am i could create a data source manually
我可以手动创建数据源吗
right like this I could actually go into
这样我实际上可以进入
spring and create a beam of type of data
弹起并创建数据类型的光束
source like so and this dailies could be
像这样的来源，这本日报可能是
you know it could be a data source that
你知道它可能是一个数据源
talks to the database now naturally I
我现在很自然地与数据库对话
know for me to be able to do that may
知道我能够做到这一点
know that I have to get access to the
知道我必须访问
types here so I'm going to get really
在这里输入，这样我就可以真正
get rid of the Maven runtime prefix I'll
摆脱Maven运行时前缀
save data source and I need some sort of
保存数据源，我需要某种
data source implementation well of
数据源实现良好
course here I could use a spring
当然在这里我可以用弹簧
framework a simple driver data source
框架一个简单的驱动程序数据源
for example like this and this is great
例如这样，这很棒
for development SDS whatever like that
用于开发SDS之类的东西
new simple driver data source and it
新的简单驱动程序数据源及其
will need in order to do its work it'll
将需要做它的工作，它将
need the driver type so we need to try
需要驱动程序类型，所以我们需要尝试
my sequel driver here so I'll say driver
我的续集司机在这里，我会说司机
equals new driver
等于新司机
and it will of course need in order for
当然，为了
it to do its work it will need let's see
它要做它的工作，我们需要看看
it throws an exception they don't need
它引发了他们不需要的异常
some configuration as well so drive it
还有一些配置，请驱动它
out to set whatever connect your L
设置任何连接您的L
properties blah blah blah and you know
属性等等等等，你知道
you put that in there driver and then
你把那个放在那里，然后
you put the URL user password etc etc
您输入URL用户密码等
etc and then return SDS and if you get
等等，然后返回SDS，如果得到
that to work
工作
you're still no one even close to doing
你仍然没人接近
it the correct way right so what we have
这是正确的方法，所以我们拥有
here is a simple driver data source the
这是一个简单的驱动程序数据源
driver did the drug data source is a
驱动程序做了药物数据源是
data source a random driver a driver is
数据源是驱动程序是随机驱动程序
what you normally it's the low-level way
通常你是低层的方式
to talk to a sequel database a driver
与续集数据库对话
will get you a connection if you connect
如果您连接，将为您建立连接
like this right so you go to Yale and
这样的权利，所以你去耶鲁
give some properties and it'll give you
给一些属性，它会给你
a connection in Java juggs a sequel
Java中的连接会产生续集
connection like that and those
那样的联系和那些
connections are expensive so this
连接很昂贵，所以这
connections are things that you want to
连接是您想要的东西
retain you don't have to recreate them
保留您不必重新创建它们
each time this simple graph data source
每次这个简单的图形数据源
is just that it's simple it's meant for
仅仅是因为它很简单
development really and the first thing
真正的发展和第一件事
you should note is that this is not a
您应该注意的是，这不是
natural connection pool it does not
自然连接池不
actually pull connections it just serves
实际上拉它只是服务的连接
as a simple replacement for a full-blown
作为成熟产品的简单替代品
connection pool implementing the same
实现相同的连接池
standard interface but creating new
标准界面，但创建新的
connections that I recall the point is
我记得重点是
if you in a test your development this
如果您正在测试您的开发，
is a okay idea but as this documentation
是个好主意，但作为本文档
spells out very plainly if you need a
如果需要，可以很清楚地说明
real connection pool outside of a Java
Java外部的真实连接池
EE container consider using Apache
EE容器考虑使用Apache
comments dbcp
注释dbcp
or c-3po or you know the Patchett
或c-3po或您知道Patchett
Tomcats got a connection pool or a call
Tomcat获得了一个连接池或一个呼叫
ECP so this has been around for a long
ECP，所以已经存在了很长时间
time but it is not by any stretch what
时间，但绝不是什么
we're going to be using so we would want
我们将要使用，所以我们想要
to configure something more robust like
配置更坚固的东西
Hikari CP or Apache Tomcat Tomcats dbcp
Hikari CP或Apache Tomcat Tomcats dbcp
or whatever um no yet just let spring
或什么都没有，只是让春天
boot do it so again in spring boot will
开机再在 spring boot
do it for us if we ask it nicely and
如果我们问得好，就为我们做
give some properties if we had on the
给一些属性，如果我们有
class path they had on the classpath h2
他们在类路径h2上拥有的类路径
or si
或si
your H sequel it will automatically
您的H续集会自动
create those data sources for us so we
为我们创建这些数据源，以便我们
don't have to do much to get that to
不必做很多事情就可以做到这一点
work but since we we don't we're not
工作，但由于我们不这样做，所以我们不是
using one of those invented ones we're
使用我们发明的那些之一
going to create our own data source
将创建我们自己的数据源
using properties so we doing here we can
使用属性，所以我们在这里可以
see that we've got properties here like
看到我们这里有一些属性
spring that data source at URL equals
使URL上的数据源等于
and here we need to tell it where to
在这里，我们需要告诉它去哪里
find our our my sequel data source and
找到我们的续集数据源，
we get give it a user name and password
我们给它一个用户名和密码
as well so springing that data source
以及这样的数据源
that URL user name data source dot user
该URL用户名数据源点用户
name
名称
okay so let's see password so it's CRM
好吧，让我们看看密码，就是CRM
CRM and the URL is JDBC : my sequel
CRM，URL是JDBC：我的续集
colon forward slash forward slash
冒号正斜杠
localhost 3306 CRM and this part always
本地主机3306 CRM，此部分始终
gets me use SSL equals false they added
让我使用SSL等于他们添加的false
this requirement a few years ago if
如果几年前有这个要求
you're for development mode if you're
如果你是开发模式
not using SSL connections and you should
不使用SSL连接，您应该
but if you're not for your local
但是如果您不适合当地人
development then you have to say user to
发展，那么你必须说用户
use SSL equals false use SSL equals
使用SSL等于false使用SSL等于
false
假
I need a host as well that's in the your
我也需要一个主机
other and we want to specify a cross
其他，我们想指定一个十字架
name driver class name in the class name
类名中的名称驱动程序类名
will be equal to call my sequel JDBC
等同于调用我的续集JDBC
driver and behind the scenes a
司机和幕后
connection pool will configure this for
连接池将为此配置
us now in spring the prior to Toledo the
我们现在在春天，在托莱多之前
connection pool is Apache Commons DB as
连接池是Apache Commons DB的
it was a Patrick Tomcat connection pool
这是一个Patrick Tomcat连接池
which is a great choice but it we've
这是一个不错的选择，但是我们已经
sound a lot of users are having better
听起来很多用户都感觉更好
luck with a car CP so we've made that
用车CP运气好，所以我们做到了
the default in spring we think it's
春天的默认值，我们认为是
faster and it works better so you you
更快，效果更好，所以你
will not notice this if anything you'll
如果您愿意，将不会注意到这一点
notice that your applications are faster
注意您的应用程序更快
right and that's good the other thing is
对，那很好，另一件事是
that we want to initialize some data so
我们想要初始化一些数据
we're going to give it some default
我们将给它一些默认值
schema and the default data sequel file
模式和默认数据续集文件
so I'm gonna go to steam it up sequel
所以我要去续集
and I did it at sequel file and spring
我是在续集文件和春季完成的
to automatically initialize the
自动初始化
application of the data source with
数据源的应用
these default files but we have to tell
这些默认文件，但我们必须告诉
it to do so for every kind of data so
它针对每种数据执行此操作
it's not just the embedded types right
不只是嵌入式类型对
so always embed it or
所以总是嵌入它或
so here we go I deleted those tables he
所以在这里我们删除了那些表
saw me delete those tables so now we
看到我删除了这些表，所以现在我们
need to create them manually so I'm
需要手动创建它们，所以我
gonna create a sequel file called schema
将创建一个名为schema的续集文件
that sequel and well go to my desktop
续集好了，然后转到我的桌面
and you can see I've got copy that data
你会看到我已经复制了这些数据
sequel downloads JBC source main
续集下载JBC源码主要
resources data that sequel copy schema
后续复制架构的资源数据
that sequel
那个续集
downloads JDBC source main resources
下载JDBC源主要资源
still my dog sequel okay so I'm just
我的狗续集还好，所以我只是
copying those two files here and you can
在这里复制这两个文件，您可以
see the tables that are created are very
看到创建的表非常
I'm very simple right the I've got two
我很简单，我有两个
types
类型
I've got two tables of customers and
我有两张桌子的顾客
orders the the two types of tables are
命令两种类型的表是
related to each other in that a customer
那个客户彼此相关
is a one-to-many side of a it's the one
是一个的一对多方面
- a one-to-many side relationship orders
-一对多关系订单
is the main side of the one-to-many
是一对多的主要方面
relationship so there are one customer
关系，所以有一个客户
and 0 to n orders that is monitored by
和0到n个订单，由
the foreign key and you know that's it
外键，你知道的就是这样
it's very straightforward I'm using my
这很简单，我正在使用我的
sequel there are some nuances with my
续集与我有些细微差别
sequel that are a little different in
续集有些不同
other databases perhaps so you might use
其他数据库，也许您可​​以使用
serial and post cars for example all
串行和邮政车，例如全部
right so we have those things that
对，所以我们有那些东西
spring boots gonna automatically click
spring boot 会自动点击
those tables for us is gonna learn that
这些桌子对我们来说将会学到
schema for us when that vacation starts
假期开始时为我们提供的模式
up now this is probably not something
现在可能不是
that you want to happen in production
您想在生产中发生的
for example so you might actually want
例如，所以您可能实际上想要
to say you know you might want to put
说你知道你可能想放
this attribute here in a you know
这个属性在这里你知道
application - dev that properties and
应用程序-开发该属性和
then make sure that when you start up
然后确保当您启动时
the application in your development
开发中的应用程序
environment you activate the spring
您激活弹簧的环境
profile called dev so that way it only
个人资料称为dev，因此仅
gets run on dev and never in production
在开发人员上运行，从不生产
back set because it'll - you know the
重新设置，因为它会-您知道
schema will destroy all the existing
模式将破坏所有现有的
data which is not a good idea indeed you
确实不是一个好主意的数据
know anybody step further you might want
知道有人可能会更进一步
to take all that and then go step
采取一切，然后走一步
further and use something like the
进一步使用诸如
liquid base or flower both of which are
液体基或花都是
database migration tools so as you
数据库迁移工具
evolve the schema you want to make sure
演化您要确保的架构
that you have the traceability to see
您具有可追溯性
what steps what changes have been made
哪些步骤进行了哪些更改
to the schema and the corvo's has ever
到方案和科尔沃的曾经
new
新
basically one that you know migrations
基本上你知道的一种迁移
that go from one schema state to the
从一个架构状态到
next and you know that way you know your
接下来，你知道那种方式，你知道你的
developer environment has schema up
开发人员环境已建立架构
until step five but your production
直到第五步，但您的生产
database only have scheme up to step two
数据库只有方案到第二步
and so the Davis migrator will know that
所以戴维斯移民会知道
the current state and the production
现状和生产
database is two and so when you deploy
数据库是两个，因此在部署时
your application for the first time and
您的申请是第一次
apply steps you know or my goal or what
应用您知道的步骤或我的目标或其他步骤
they call migrations step three four
他们称迁移为第三步，第四步
five right the result will be that your
五正确的结果是，你的
system will be brought up to about up to
系统将被提升到大约
two to the current state of the
两个到当前状态
development code and that gets run every
开发代码，并且每次运行
single time and so there's also nice you
一次，所以你也很高兴
know some of them over reason why they
了解其中一些原因
give you ways to model rollback and so
给您建模回滚的方法等等
on so what a really good support there
所以那里真的有很好的支持
now that's perhaps a video for another
现在也许是另一个的视频
time for our purposes today this will
今天为了我们的目的，这将
this will get us what we want now that
这将使我们得到我们现在想要的
said what do you want take advantage
说你想利用什么
we're a puppet you should feel free to
我们是人偶，你应该随便
take advantage of your IDE support for
利用您的IDE支持
different databases my entire jail has
我整个监狱都有不同的数据库
pretty good support here for working
这里工作的很好的支持
with different databases it even has a
与不同的数据库甚至有一个
separate product a whole separate
分开的产品
products that you can buy or I think
您可以购买或我认为的产品
there might be an open-source version
可能有一个开源版本
I'm not sure but there's certainly a
我不确定，但肯定有
version that you can buy that will that
您可以购买的版本
will let you work with your different
让您与众不同
databases so I've got a let's see CRM
数据库，让我们来看看CRM
password test good so now I'm connected
密码测试良好，所以现在我已连接
and the result of that is I get a
结果是我得到了
console here so I can say you know show
控制台在这里，所以我可以说你知道表演
tables run that you can see there's
运行表，您可以看到
nothing there
那里空无一物
alright so let's run this application
好吧，让我们运行这个应用程序
just run it doing nothing else just fund
只是运行它而已
the application all right and when I go
好的应用程序，当我去的时候
back to here to my sequel console
回到这里到我的续集控制台
database tools console tip and I want to
数据库工具控制台提示，我想
run the out yeah
用光是的
create game
创建游戏
there we go so I can see I've got those
我们去那里，所以我可以看到我有那些
two two tables there and I've got some
那里有两个两张桌子，我有一些
data right so if you just look at my
数据正确，所以如果你看看我的
schema I've got this the definition of
模式我已经有了这个的定义
the objects India and the database and
对象印度和数据库以及
data Ivan about what is it now one two
数据伊万现在是什么一二
three six records and I've got David I
三六个记录，我有大卫一世
being written or is being written for
正在写或正在写
myself Josh for Jane and for Bob and for
我是乔什（Josh）的简（Jane）和鲍勃（Bob）的
Michelle so Michelle has three Bob has
米歇尔，所以米歇尔有三个鲍勃
to obtain has two and Josh has three
获得两个，乔希有三个
records okay so some of them have zero
记录还可以，所以其中一些为零
that's very important we'll come back to
这很重要，我们将回到
that later now what we want to do is we
现在稍后我们要做的是
want to exercise you know to be an
想锻炼你知道的
application that takes advantage of some
利用某些优势的应用程序
of the basic support in Springfield
Springfield的基本支持
itself so we're gonna start simple go
本身，所以我们要开始简单
with what we know and and walk our way
用我们所知道并走的路
up through more interesting more
通过更多有趣的更多
sophisticated more perhaps exotic offers
复杂的，也许是奇特的报价
options for the JDBC accessing spring
JDBC访问spring的选项
get over when you do a lot of similar
做很多类似的事情时要克服
demos but we're gonna do you know I'm
演示，但我们要知道我
gonna duplicate I'm gonna write a lot of
要重复，我要写很多
similar things in the same code page
同一代码页中的类似内容
here so I'm gonna create a really neat
在这里，我要创造一个非常整洁的
ility here just to write out the line to
这里的灵活性只是为了写出
try that alliance that we can see where
尝试那个联盟，我们可以看到哪里
the output we are so line and all we're
我们的输出如此行而已
gonna do is just use the log4j longer
要做的就是使用log4j更长的时间
there I'll say it long touch info and
在那里，我会说很长一段时间的信息，
I'll just print out a line all right
我会打印一行
there we are very simple now let's say
那里我们很简单，现在说
that in our first example we're going to
在第一个示例中，我们将要
have a application runner that's a beam
有一个应用程序运行器是光束
that will start up and it will log out
那将启动，它将注销
information in the database we're gonna
数据库中的信息
produce a report so I'm gonna create the
产生一份报告，所以我要创建
customers and orders count and it's
客户和订单计数，这是
going to be an application runner I you
我将成为应用程序赛跑者
know this should be it could be a unit
知道这应该是一个单位
test or something but we're just trying
测试之类的东西，但我们只是在尝试
to demonstrate how different things work
展示不同事物如何运作
so our application runner is going to
所以我们的应用程序运行者将
take advantage of this case the JDBC
利用这种情况，JDBC
template now the JDBC template is the I
现在的JDBC模板是I
think one the most interesting sort of
认为最有趣的一种
objects in the JDBC is support and
JDBC中的对象是支持和
spring
弹簧
been around forever in the day and it
在一天中永远存在
makes short work of
使短期工作
a lot of the things involved in working
工作中涉及很多事情
with sequels so let's there's a you know
与续集，所以让我们有一个
if you look at the spring documentation
如果您查看Spring文档
here spring that IO for side projects
在这里春天，IO用于辅助项目
floor sash Spring Framework look at the
地板窗框Spring Framework看看
data access documentation go to data
数据访问文档转到数据
access with JDBC you'll see this amazing
使用JDBC进行访问，您会发现这很神奇
rubric this table here that miss all the
专栏这张桌子错过了所有
things that are required for any
任何必需的东西
interaction with sequel with a JDBC
通过JDBC与续集进行交互
sequel connection and resource when
续集连接和资源何时
you're working with JDBC and all the
您正在使用JDBC等
things that you have to manage they have
您必须管理的东西
to define connection parameters open the
定义连接参数，打开
connection specify the sequel primers or
连接说明续集引物或
statement rather defined include
定义较为明确的陈述包括
declared parameters and provide
声明参数并提供
parameter values prepare and execute the
参数值准备并执行
statement setup any set up and loop
语句设置任何设置和循环
through the results of any do the work
通过任何工作的结果
on each iteration processing exceptions
在每次迭代中处理异常
and all transactions close the
并且所有交易关闭
connection statement end result set not
连接语句最终结果集不正确
to mention the transaction you have to
提及您必须进行的交易
come in it so analyst stuff is stuff
进来吧，所以分析师的东西就是东西
that has to be done well of course
当然要做好
spring makes you know all but for those
春天让你知道，除了那些
things go away and it calls you back or
事情消失了，它回叫你
the possible for the things that you
你所可能做的事情
really should be involved with right so
真的应该参与其中，所以
things like specifying the secret
诸如指定秘密之类的事情
statement that's naturally very
这种说法自然很
important that's the thing you're here
重要的是您在这里
to do right is to provide a custom query
正确的做法是提供自定义查询
you're here to define parameters that go
你在这里定义去的参数
into the sequel proto statement fair
进入续集原始陈述集
enough right and we are here to do the
足够的权利，我们在这里做
look obviously the defining connection
看起来很明显的定义联系
for each planners for the defining the
为每个计划者定义
connection parameters we've only done
我们只做的连接参数
that like we did that here that was I'm
就像我们在这里所做的那样
not gonna say it was easy but it wasn't
不会说这很容易，但事实并非如此
hard either like I mean you know the
很难，就像我的意思是你知道
hard part was actually setting up the
困难的部分实际上是建立
database itself in my sequel certainly
数据库本身肯定在我的续集中
not this right so we have a JDBC
没有这个权利，所以我们有一个JDBC
template and it's you know it's gonna do
模板，这是你知道的
a lot of things that we don't want to do
很多我们不想做的事情
so let's say stream line utils dot line
所以说流线utils点线
good and what we're gonna do is one of
好，我们要做的是其中之一
create all of the data in the database
创建数据库中的所有数据
and generator of pork and the report
猪肉的生产者和报告
will have information about each
将有关于每个的信息
customer and Ali orders are assigned to
客户和阿里订单分配给
them so public static class customer
他们是公共静态类的客户
order report and we'll have the string
订单报告，我们将获得字符串
name email private int order
姓名电子邮件私人int订单
count and the long ID alright so that's
计数和长ID好吧，那是
the what is that the customer ID I guess
我猜那是什么客户ID
we could call that to be very specific
我们可以称之为非常具体
so they were putting a detail around
所以他们把细节
this report data now in order to
现在该报告数据是为了
generate that query I'll have a query
生成该查询，我将有一个查询
that looks like this select see that
看起来像这个选择看到
asterisk and I'm going to select the a
星号，我将选择一个
sub query have sub quick that counts the
子查询具有子快速计数
the number of errors for that for that a
该a的错误数量
customer so select count
客户，请选择数量
oh that ID from orders oh we're old at
哦，订单中的ID哦，我们老了
customer underscore FK equals C ID write
客户下划线FK等于C ID写
as count so let's see what we get so now
作为计数，所以让我们看看我们现在得到了什么
I'll end up sequel statement using the
我将使用
JDBC template so here TVC template that
JDBC模板，所以这里是TVC模板
query we don't want to get we don't
查询我们不想得到我们不
equate for the whole object there's a
等同于整个对象
whole bunch of methods here by the way
顺便说一句整个方法
so I'm going to cover some of my
所以我要讲一些我的
favorites but most of the time I'm using
最喜欢的，但是大多数时候我都在使用
query and sometimes I'll use update or
查询，有时我会使用update或
execute but there's a whole bunch of
执行，但有一堆
variants at them so we'll talk about
他们的变体，所以我们将讨论
some them today so we'll put this in
今天一些，所以我们把它放在
here and the second parameter is a real
在这里，第二个参数是一个实数
mapper now a real mapper is what real
映射器现在一个真正的映射器是什么
map is useful if the if the data that
如果数据是
you're returning if the results of the
如果返回的结果是
query that you're returning
查询您要返回的
map one-to-one to an object so if each
一对一映射到一个对象，所以如果每个
record in the result set maps to an
结果集中的记录映射到
object then you should use a real mapper
对象，那么您应该使用一个真实的映射器
right because you can map them directly
对，因为您可以直接映射它们
to objects so I'm gonna get back a
物体，所以我要回去
collection of customer order reports
客户订单报告的收集
like this and in order for me to get
这样，让我得到
back get that back merit look at how
回来得到那个优点，看看如何
smart until it is it's now aware of the
聪明，直到它现在意识到
fact that you know I'm making a query
你知道我正在查询的事实
against my local resource so I can
依靠我当地的资源，所以我可以
actually click on for example Oda
实际点击例如织田
customer to F ok or this kind of thing
客户同意或类似的事情
right here and it'll be smart up to see
在这里，它会很聪明地看到
what I'm trying to do so what is it
我正在尝试做的是什么
saying
说
I don't lose all customers why do you
我不会失去所有客户，为什么你
think that is
认为那是
easy it's pretty smart Oh Kate a second
很简单，很聪明哦，凯特
I guess let's see close that down and
我想让我们来看看
we'll open them up again hmm well guess
我们将再次打开它们
it's a I'm not sure it doesn't matter
我不确定这没关系
either wait musics pretty smart and you
要么等待音乐非常聪明，你
can actually come and click on tokens in
可以真正来点击令牌
the sequel statement and it'll it'll
续集声明，它将
know what you're trying to do so now I'm
知道你现在想做什么
given a callback each time it so it's
每次都给一个回调，所以
gonna visit I'm gonna give the crate and
去拜访我要给箱子
then it's gonna loop through all the
然后它将遍历所有
records and it's going to call my whim
记录，这将使我心血来潮
ever back this is an interface right and
永远回来这是一个正确的接口，
the interface is a back that's a each
界面是背面
time I get a result set just in the past
我得到过去的结果集的时间
the result set plus the current row
结果集加上当前行
number and I can do it if I want with it
数字，如果我愿意，我可以做
but it wants me to map that into a
但它希望我将其映射到
custom order put so here I'm gonna say
自定义订单，所以在这里我要说
alright you know the first one the ID
好吧，你知道第一个ID
that comes back let's call this ID the
回来后，我们将此ID称为
idea that comes back and then the
想法回来，然后
artists get string name and all that
艺术家获得字符串名称以及所有这些
gets string email and then honest get
获取字符串电子邮件，然后诚实获取
wrong count all right so we can call
算错了好吧，我们可以打电话
this tally if you want doesn't matter
如果你想要的话没关系
but it has to match whatever we
但是它必须匹配我们
specified up here okay so with that done
在这里指定好了，这样就完成了
one thing to keep in mind is that this
要记住的一件事是
API is super old
API太旧了
alright this API was look at this this
好吧，这个API就是看这个
was written originally 2001 so this is a
最初写于2001年，所以这是
17 year old API and yet it works even
已有17年历史的API，但它甚至可以正常工作
better today than it did when it was
今天比以前更好
first conceived you see these car back
首先想到你看到这些车回来
interfaces this is a template object
接口这是一个模板对象
right after the design pattern the
在设计模式之后
template object and basically fill it
模板对象并基本上填充它
you know you fill out the parts that
你知道你填写了
matter to you and it does the rest
对你很重要，其余的事
including all the transaction management
包括所有交易管理
resource the initialization in that
资源中的初始化
position and destruction all that kind
那种定位和破坏
of stuff is done for you and the result
的东西已经为您完成，结果
is that you just played in the parts
就是你只是扮演角色
that you care about well historically
你在历史上很在意
prior to Java 5 sorry Gadwal 8
Java 5之前的版本对不起Gadwal 8
historically that that would have been
从历史上讲，那本来是
anonymous interfaces like this oh now
像这样的匿名接口
these interfaces lend themselves to
这些接口适合
lambdas which i think is a really really
我认为这是真的
convenient so what do we have here
方便，所以我们这里有什么
inte all right look at that it's a
好的，请看这是一个
couldn't you know couldn't have ended up
你不知道不可能结束吗
better I think it's just really nice
更好，我认为这真的很好
that this API just works so nicely with
该API可以很好地与
this uh with lambdas in Java so now we
Java中的lambdas这个呃，所以现在我们
have the reports and we're gonna say for
有报告，我们要说
each and we're just gonna print that
每个，我们只是要打印出来
each one all right I'm gonna use a log4j
每一个都好，我要使用log4j
logger okay this is Lombok I'm using a
记录器好吧，这是龙目岛，我正在使用
loan book to to synthesize these fields
贷款簿以综合这些领域
at compile time and it's as though I've
在编译时，好像我已经
written them myself okay let's see what
我自己写给他们，好吧，让我们看看
that gets us let's run this application
让我们运行该应用程序
all right didn't get this there's our
好吧没有得到这是我们的
six records alright so there we got the
六个记录好了，所以我们得到了
records we can see that's working we can
记录，我们可以看到它正在工作，我们可以
see I can only count to three etc right
看我只能数到三等
good very simple you've probably seen
很好，很简单，您可能已经看过
something like that before
像以前那样
let's go a little bit further and now
让我们再往前走一点
let's do a one-to-many so this is
让我们做一对多，这是
actually pretty simple each record that
实际上，每条记录都非常简单
we got back in the result set
我们回到了结果集中
mapped to an object so that was simple
映射到一个对象，这很简单
now we're gonna do a one-to-many where
现在我们要做一对多
each record might have to roll up into a
每个记录可能必须汇总到一个
aggregate our customers are going to get
聚集我们的客户将获得
all the customers and all the errors and
所有的客户和所有的错误和
we don't want to do something
我们不想做某事
inefficient we don't want to set all the
效率低下，我们不想设置所有
customers and then visit each one in a
客户，然后访问每个
loop and then do a select all in the
循环，然后在
database that has for all the records
具有所有记录的数据库
that max out that'll be very inefficient
那最大的效率会很低
we do we went into the n plus one
我们做到了n加一
problem so rather than do that let's do
问题，而不是那样做，让我们去做
a create customers and orders example
创建客户和订单的示例
without the count so we've said we're
没有数，所以我们说我们
gonna actually get the oil the the
实际上会得到油
orders themselves okay and same as
命令自己还好，和
before when you use the JDBC template
在使用JDBC模板之前
okay and we're gonna use the JB's
好的，我们将使用JB的
template to make the call up to the
进行呼叫的模板
database so we want to say string utils
数据库，所以我们想说字符串utils
lines okay and
线还可以
we're going to say this that Jamie's
我们要说的是杰米的
tell it that query select see that I D
告诉它查询选择看到该ID
di as CID Oh that ID as oh I D and O
di作为CID哦，那个ID作为oh ID和O
that asterisk didn't want to see that
星号不想看到
asterisk why not see that asterisk from
星号为什么不从中看到那个星号
from customers see left join orders o on
从客户那里看到左加入订单o
see that ID equals o dat customers FK
看到ID等于老客户FK
alright so we're doing the left outer
好吧，所以我们在做左外
join here and we're gonna get back you
加入这里，我们将带你回去
know if you can imagine it we're gonna
知道你能想象得到的吗
get back you know let's see we're gonna
回来，你知道让我们看看我们会
get back you know row you know Josh josh
回来，你知道行，你知道Josh josh
Josh um you know and then let's say one
乔希，你知道，然后再说一个
and we'll have the it'll be merged
然后我们将其合并
together with the results for the order
连同订单结果
so it'll be ABC and then you know OID
所以会是ABC，然后您就会知道OID
will be equal to 1 etcetera so I'll have
等于1 etcetera，所以我有
that and then the next line will be
那然后下一行将是
largely the same except this will be 2
基本相同，除了这将是2
and this will be d e f and the next line
这将是def和下一行
will be G you know F G H I etc so all
会是G，你知道FGHI等，所以
the information from the customer is
来自客户的信息是
here it's on the Left column short of
这是在左列不足
last two columns but everything after
最后两列，但之后的所有内容
that is the order ID so what wouldn't do
那是订单ID，所以怎么办
is women do a left outer join which
女人是在做左外连接吗
means that we'll get at least the
意味着我们至少会得到
information from this once and this
一次又一次的信息
might be null if there's no orders if
如果没有订单，则可能为null
there are made in one order if there's
如果有
more than one order that will have
一个以上的订单
duplicate records on the left right all
重复记录在左侧所有
these all this information left is
这些剩下的所有这些信息是
duplicate but we get their real
复制但我们得到他们的真实
information that we care about the
我们关心的信息
orders here now as we get to another
现在我们到达另一个订单
record like this then we'll start to see
像这样录制然后我们将开始看到
you know the primary you know this might
你知道小学的，你可能知道
be will loop what was it Jane I guess so
会循环简，我猜是什么
Jane and Jane Jane calm write cetera so
简和简简冷静写作等等
it'll be James information
这将是詹姆斯的信息
and she might have you know different
她可能会让你知道与众不同
orders or whatever so and there might be
订单等等
the same skill okay so in this case
同样的技能好吧，在这种情况下
we're going to loop through all the
我们将遍历所有
records and whenever one of the records
记录以及任何记录之一
is whether whatever the ID of the
是无论
customer is different as is here or
客户与这里不同，或者
break we're quite a new aggregate object
打破，我们是一个新的聚合对象
and accumulate and end and the meantime
并积累和结束，与此同时
as we're going through and the idea is
正如我们正在经历的，想法是
the same we're going to cumulate all the
同样，我们将累积所有
records into the aggregate that we've
记录到我们已经汇总
created so i'm going to create an
创建了，所以我要创建一个
aggregate starting starting here
聚合从此处开始
aggregate i mean i'd get the king the
总的来说，我的意思是我会得到国王
credit the orders aggregate again and so
再次记入订单汇总，因此
on all right so when go down the line
好的，所以当下线时
and tell eventually we have all the data
并告诉最终我们拥有所有数据
in a in a collection of information well
在信息收集中
that means that we have to be able to
这意味着我们必须能够
iterate through the different records
遍历不同的记录
until we can meet a certain criteria
直到我们满足特定条件
which means that the is that the real
这意味着真正的
map approach that we used before it
我们之前使用的地图方法
doesn't quite work here we need
我们在这里工作不充分
something that gives us the ability to
使我们有能力
iterate over the data so here we use a
遍历数据，所以在这里我们使用
result set extractor okay so i'm going
结果集提取器好，所以我要去
to create a result set extractor to
创建结果集提取器以
create a collection of customer records
创建客户记录的集合
so we need a customer type i guess we
所以我们需要一个客户类型
can use this as a basis but it's not the
可以以此为基础，但这不是
final representation by any stretch
任何延伸的最终代表
can't customer and what just the ID and
不能客户，什么是ID和
we need and so the talent we want a set
我们需要，所以我们想要一套人才
of orders some orders equals new hash
的订单有些订单等于新的哈希
set
组
[Applause]
[掌声]
public static class order private string
公共静态类顺序私有字符串
private long ID private string still
私人长ID私人字符串仍然
skew all right good for that so okay
偏斜对这个有好处，好吗
we've got the customer we've got the
我们有客户，我们有
order now now we've got those two things
现在订购，我们已经有了这两件事
and what we want to do is when I could
我们想要做的是
it was extractor that visits every
是提取器访问每个
single one of those records in
这些记录中的一个
influences logic that we just described
影响我们刚刚描述的逻辑
here and is a little confusing
在这里，有点混乱
but I think it's kind of easy to
但我认为这很容易
understand when you kind of see it in
了解您何时会看到它
action so first things first we start
行动，所以首先我们开始
the while loop right so let's type the
while循环正确，所以我们键入
while loop here Wow our dad has next
while循环在这里哇，我们父亲有下一个
let's visit each record now we have a
让我们访问每个记录，现在我们有一个
condition we have to accumulate so let's
我们必须积累的条件，让我们
get the current ID ID equals honest that
得到当前的ID ID等于说实话
get long and that'll be the customer ID
久了，那将是客户ID
sub C accumulate and now we're gonna say
sub C积累了，现在我们要说
while our now stop next and then we have
当我们现在停下来，然后我们有
a condition we say if the current
我们说一个条件，如果当前
customer which we haven't defined yet so
我们尚未定义的客户
we're gonna create a current customer
我们将创建一个当前客户
let's just say this one if current
让我们说这个，如果当前
customer if the current customer should
客户，如果当前客户应该
equal null or current customer get ID
等于null或当前客户获取ID
does not equal ID right and then for
不等于ID正确，然后
this to work we also need to order this
这个工作，我们还需要订购这个
by ID don't we so we need to see ordered
根据ID，我们不是，所以我们需要查看订单
by CID that way it's always gonna be in
通过CID，它将始终存在
that order so our se is that we are okay
那个顺序，所以我们的意思是我们还好
and that gets us by the way this will
而这将使我们
give us a customer collection just as we
给我们一个客户集合，就像我们
want okay
想要好的
and there's our there's our
有我们的有我们的
and told you you can kind of confusing
告诉你你可能会感到困惑
me take okay you know we have this and
我同意，你知道我们有这个，
now we're saying if this has been null
现在我们说这是否为空
if it's null or current customer does
如果为空或当前客户
not equal ID then we paid a current
ID不相等，则我们支付了当前
customer so current customer equals and
客户，因此当前客户等于
we have to create a new customer out of
我们必须创建一个新客户
that result sets our new customer and
结果设置了我们的新客户，
we're gonna give it a result set we have
我们要给它一个结果集
the information here so honest get long
这里的信息很诚实
CID RS get string name RS get string
CID RS获取字符串名称RS获取字符串
email and then a new hash set for the
电子邮件，然后为
orders I'm going to add things to that
订单，我要添加一些东西
as we go through now current customer
当我们经历现在的客户时
dot get orders well we have to map the
点得到订单好，我们必须映射
current information if there is any for
当前信息（如果有）
that record so when a we're going to
该记录，所以当我们要
create a order once we have our order so
一旦有订单就创建订单
we have to actually get the order out of
我们必须从订单中取出订单
the current result and try and create
当前结果并尝试创建
it's our new order and the order is
这是我们的新订单，订单是
expecting an ID and a SKU so let's do
期待一个ID和一个SKU，让我们开始吧
some defensive coding here we're gonna
一些防御性编码，我们要
say c RS get long o ID and string SKU
说c RS获得长o ID和字符串SKU
equals R in stock get string X Q so now
等于R的股票得到字符串XQ，所以现在
we're saying create the OID and skew so
我们是说创建OID并倾斜
if all aidid is not equal null
如果所有aidid不等于null
all right
好吧
always true probably not always true all
永远都是正确的，也许并非永远都是真的
right I'll get long good throw an
好吧，我会好好投掷
exception I suppose so either way we
我想是例外，无论如何
don't wanna worry about that but we want
不想为此担心，但我们想要
to add these things to the to the
将这些东西添加到
current collection so we wrap it in
当前集合，所以我们将其包装
order and basically want to create it
订单，基本上想创建它
only if it's valid right so we're gonna
只有当它是正确的权利，所以我们会
say now current customer that get orders
现在说获得订单的当前客户
that add equals order right so they're
加上等于顺序的权利，所以他们
moving through your data and we're
遍历您的数据，我们
making sure that as we add data that
确保在添加数据时
that when you accumulated into the
当你积累到
orders collection then now I want to
现在要收集订单
steal all the customers that we've got
窃取我们拥有的所有客户
right because we're going to we're gonna
对，因为我们要去
eventually hit this condition where we
最终达到这种条件，我们
have to reset the customer so I'm gonna
必须重置客户，所以我要
save the customer often to a somebody
经常将客户保存给某人
get it later on so I'm going to stir it
待会儿再来，所以我要搅拌一下
in terms of its in terms of the primary
在主要方面
key for the customer there and we'll
客户在那里的钥匙，我们将
come back to it later so customers map
稍后再回来，以便客户映射
equals new hash map remember to changes
等于新的哈希图，记住要更改
into a concurrent map if you ever have
进入并发映射（如果有）
to make this multi-threaded and
使这个多线程和
concurrent I can custom a map and if
并发我可以自定义地图，如果
that's not normal blah blah good
那不是正常的，等等，很好
and then custom a map so this is gonna
然后自定义地图，这样
we're gonna hit the same path again and
我们将再次走同样的路，
again multiple times so in theory want
再次多次，所以理论上想要
to call put those many orders is there
打电话给那么多订单
all which might result in some we've
所有这些都可能导致我们
done inputs but again it's by key so
完成输入，但同样是按键操作
it'll never get it's not one to
它永远不会得到它不是一个
something we're gonna add you know more
我们会加一些东西，让您知道更多
customers or the same keys so uh well
客户或相同的密钥，所以很好
take advantage of that later on alright
稍后再利用它
so there you go there's our our current
所以你去那里就是我们当前的
logic that's our you know and then funny
我们知道的逻辑然后又有趣
to return the data I guess a return
返回数据我想返回
customer map dot values that gives us a
客户地图点值使我们
collection of customers all right so
这样可以收集客户
what is it wrong with this while
这是怎么了
RS that next oh I don't know looks like
RS那下一个我不知道的样子
it should look to me hmm
它应该在我看来
well I don't know intelligent will have
好吧，我不知道智能会不会
to disagree agree to disagree here my
不同意我不同意
friend so we've got now this while loop
朋友，所以我们现在有了这个while循环
and ah that's why it doesn't loop yeah
而这就是为什么它不会循环的原因
you're right so get rid of that and we
你是对的，所以摆脱它，我们
have now our simple logic our simple
现在有了我们简单的逻辑
logic that uh well accumulate everything
很好地积累一切的逻辑
for us now again this is pretty tedious
对我们而言，这再次非常繁琐
it's a little complicated but it sure
这有点复杂，但可以肯定
beats um managing all the transactions
胜过管理所有交易
and doing this right so at least we're
并正确地做到这一点，至少我们
getting some gain out of this and again
从中获得一些收益
this also lends itself to being a lambda
这也使自己成为lambda
so we write that a little bit there you
所以我们在那儿写一点
go there's our result set extractor and
去那里是我们的结果集提取器，
we're gonna use the result six result
我们将使用结果六结果
set extractor here to get the data so
在这里设置提取器以获取数据
now say customers that for each log info
现在向客户说每个日志信息
then again we left the logger and we get
然后我们又离开了记录仪，我们得到了
the logger by log4j to okay so there you
通过log4j记录器可以，所以在那里
got let's see what that gives us and
让我们看看它给我们带来了什么
Mariano start ordering these so that we
马里亚诺开始订购这些，以便我们
can notice see the latest in greatest
可以看到最伟大的最新消息
last since we're having multiple these
最后，因为我们有多个
application runners so let me go back
应用程序运行者，让我回头
and make this number one so it starts up
并让这个数字一开始
first released reset the application and
首先发布，重置应用程序，然后
what did I do
我做了什么
see I'm customers doesn't exist did I do
看到我不存在客户吗
that I don't know
我不知道
Oh kutiman haha okay good so intelligent
哦kutiman哈哈好的好聪明
wasn't crazy it's me I I this is now
不是疯了，现在是我
twice that I have second-guessed Eid
我曾两次猜测开斋节
tonight and I've been wrong that's not
今晚，我错了，那不是
good orders well that one's clearly
好订单，很明显
there let's see if I doing something
看看我是否在做某事
silly here left joined orders oh oh
傻在这里留下加盟订单哦哦
let's try it again
让我们再试一次
source main resources data its sequel
源主要资源数据及其续集
schema that sequel sexy IDs see that I
续集性感ID的架构会看到我
repeat orders OID okay
重复订单OID可以
left - an orzo uncie that ID goes oh
左-ID消失的偶像哦
that customers FK so data schema
客户FK这样的数据模式
customer FK and my friend Lucas editor
客户FK和我的朋友Lucas编辑
he's the creator of Jacobs the driver
他是驾驶员Jacobs的创造者
object-oriented query API I'm sure just
面向对象的查询API我敢肯定
laughing at me now saying that this is
现在嘲笑我说这是
exactly why you should used typesafe
到底为什么要使用类型安全
sequel as as enable through Java or
通过Java启用的续集或
queue and he might have a good point
排队，他可能有一个好点
there so that's a good reason to go see
在那里，这是一个很好的理由去看看
the other spring tip video I did on that
我在那做的另一个 spring 技巧 视频
and also my beetus so it's just another
还有我的蜜蜂，所以这只是另一个
sequel centric or M type thing like my
以续集为中心或M型的东西
like a like Java OQ alright so see that
像Java OQ这样的，好吧，
ID a CID okay let's see if this gives us
ID CID好吧，让我们看看这是否给我们
the results that we're expecting always
我们一直期望的结果
use your tools when you can that looks
尽可能使用自己的工具
like it's gonna work that should be fine
像它会工作应该很好
so
所以
yeah that should be exactly what we
是的，那应该正是我们
expect so let's go ahead and now run
期待，让我们继续，现在运行
this code again ha ha they cool so there
这段代码再次哈哈，他们很酷，所以那里
you go those are there's the results
你去那些有结果
that we expected except what happened
我们所期望的，除了发生了什么
there are is e so in the loop
循环中有e
wait a minute where's my sequel
等一下我的续集在哪
statement here run this again yeah that
声明在这里再次运行这个是的
looks right so we should have we should
看起来不错，所以我们应该拥有我们应该
have
有
oh I've done this twice no kidding
哦，我已经两次没有开玩笑了
okay somehow I did that twice in there
好吧，我在那里做了两次
okay so we were in this program one more
好，所以我们又参加了这个程序
time that she looks and when it was a
她看起来的时间以及那是什么时候
little tease okay
小挑逗好吗
oh there we go look at that so now we
哦，我们去看看那个，所以现在我们
have six records as we expect that some
有六个记录，正如我们期望的那样
of them have data and some do not
其中有数据，而有些则没有
so orders as an order with to 0 and no
因此，定单作为具有0到no的订单
why is that so when I say if Heidi's not
为什么这样，当我说如果海蒂不是
equal to null and look at the results
等于null并查看结果
from this close that
从这个结束
if the customer FK is no let's try that
如果客户FK否，请尝试
one
一
why does it why is the IDE so sure that
为什么呢？为什么IDE如此确定
that should be none oh okay
那应该没有哦，好吧
i D all right
我可以
ah let it go much better okay so we can
啊，让它变得更好，好吧，我们可以
see empty orders empty orders but we
看到空订单空订单，但我们
have orders for the rest of them okay so
剩下的订单都可以了
now we have a very simple example we
现在我们有一个非常简单的例子
have a one-to-many relationship and yeah
有一对多的关系，是的
that was a little tedious it was a it
那有点乏味，那是一个
took a little mental gymnastics to make
进行了一些心理体操
that look but we understood what we're
那个样子，但我们了解我们在做什么
doing and then it's far cleaner than if
这样做，然后比如果
you had to do it by ourselves manually
您必须手动完成
so I'm glad we had the opportunity to do
所以我很高兴我们有机会做
this because it does demonstrate what
这是因为它确实展示了什么
could be worse now that's said this is
现在可能会更糟，这就是
not the only way to do this actually
实际上并非唯一的方法
there's actually some some room for
实际上还有一些空间
improvement here even within this
即使在这里也有所改善
example so let's take this example one
示例，让我们以这个示例为例
step further I'm gonna use a third-party
更进一步，我将使用第三方
ecosystem library called simple flat
生态系统图书馆称为简单公寓
mapper okay know this let's see this
映射器好吧，知道这个，让我们看看这个
example we're gonna name simple flat
例子，我们要命名简单的公寓
mapper
映射器
let's be ordered three same basic domain
让我们订购三个相同的基本域
model we're just gonna use a third-party
模型，我们只是要使用第三方
library here called simple flat mapper
这里的库称为简单平面映射器
and I don't have it on the cross path
我没有在十字路口
just yet and it is unfortunately not a
只是，现在还不是
checkbox for it now simple thought
现在它的复选框很简单
mapper is a product worth mentioning
映射器是值得一提的产品
it's a third party project that um that
这是一个第三方项目
allows you to map data via you know CSV
允许您通过知道CSV的方式映射数据
data X and all data whatever sequel data
数据X和所有数据（无论后续数据）
and it integrates with a number of
它与许多
different interesting libraries out
各种有趣的图书馆
there so and you know one of those
在那里，你知道其中之一
integrations of course is spring so what
整合当然是春天了，那又如何呢？
is it 3.1 8.0 I think there we are so
是3.1 8.0，我认为我们是如此
we're gonna use this and we use a simple
我们将使用这个，我们使用一个简单的
thought mapper
思维导图
to make all of this terrible code to go
使所有这些可怕的代码
away right so it comes much simpler the
就走了，所以它变得简单得多
code is now just a few short lines what
现在的代码只是几行
we're gonna do is we're gonna replace
我们要做的是替换
all that logic all that manual
所有逻辑所有手册
accumulation logic with a result set
结果集的累加逻辑
extractor that's created for us using
使用我们为我们创建的提取器
simplified never so RS e equals JDBC
简化，永不让RS e等于JDBC
template Joosten was a mapper factory
模板Joosten是一个制图厂
dot new instance dot add keys
点新实例点添加键
and the key is the ID that's the key
钥匙就是钥匙
that we want to break on right the
我们想在右边打破
accumulation key and then the new
积累密钥，然后新
results that extractor will be of type
提取器将是类型的结果
not user customer duck class all right
不是用户客户的鸭子类就可以了
is that right
那正确吗
looks right new instance is it
看起来不错，是新实例
referencing the right customer looks
引用正确的客户外观
okay to me
对我好
well it's an implicit okay it's it's
好吧，这是一个隐含的好吧，因为
from that one in particular is it not
从那个特别是不是
yeah result to extract her other term
是的结果是提取了她的另一个词
spring okay and basically I can I have
春天还好，基本上我可以
to rewrite the quiz just a little bit
重写测验一点点
here to reflect this you know to reflect
在这里反映这一点，你知道要反映
the fact that it's being managed for us
为我们管理的事实
by this convention based thing but it's
通过这个基于约定的东西，但这是
not a big deal so what we do is we say
没什么大不了的，所以我们要做的是说
select CID as ID and let's write this
选择CID作为ID，让我们写这个
create a little bit here
在这里创建一点
sexy IDs ID see that name as name see
sexy IDs ID看到的名字就是名字
that email as email old a tidy as orders
那个电子邮件像电子邮件一样整洁有序
so again the collection you know the one
再一次，你知道一个收藏
to many parts the many part is the
在很多方面，很多方面是
collection orders ID of each order is
每个订单的托收订单ID为
called a ID so it's orders underscore ID
叫一个ID，所以它的订单下划线是ID
o dot SKU as orders SKU and from
o点SKU作为订单SKU，并从
customers see left join let's join
客户看到左加入我们加入
orders o on C dot customer FK equals o
C点客户FK上的订单o等于o
ID order by see that ID alright next it
通过ID顺序查看ID旁边的ID
looks fine to me let's try this now and
对我来说看起来不错，让我们现在尝试一下，
we should have this give the same
我们应该给这个
results as we had before
像以前一样的结果
let's see we're already wrong see oh
让我们看看我们已经错了哦
sorry
抱歉
oh that Oh
哦那个哦
that equals see that I D get those
等于看到ID得到那些
things backwards
事情倒退
good look at that not bad did I actually
好看，我还不错
yeah I did so if you look at this we can
是的，我这样做了，如果你看看这个，我们可以
see that in this case it wasn't so
看到在这种情况下不是这样
enough to create no order to empty out
足以创建无订单清空
the rows right so that's a little bit of
正确的行，所以有点
a bummer you can actually visit the
真可惜你可以参观
records and and see if they're if
记录并查看是否
they're no for example let's see left
他们不是，例如让我们左看
outer join does that make a difference I
外连接确实有所作为我
wonder if it makes a difference here now
想知道现在是否在这里有所作为
it gave us Knowles which is a bit
它给了我们诺尔斯，这有点
unfortunate but again you can you get
不幸的是，但是你可以再次得到
99% that code there automatically and
99％的代码会自动在那里
all you'd have to do is to visit the
您所要做的就是访问
results and then send that back to the
结果，然后将其发送回
customer right so I could say customer
客户对，所以我可以说客户
thought stream dot map and you know see
思想流点图，你知道看
see that get orders stream you know you
看到获取订单流，您知道您
can replace it right so I'm gonna you're
可以取代它，所以我会你
gonna filter each one like so then
要像这样过滤每个人，然后
you're gonna say I'm C dot orders dot
你会说我是C点订单点
stream that has or count right you'll
拥有或拥有权利的流
see any match
看到任何比赛
oh oh that get ID should equal null
哦，哦，获取ID应该等于null
right boolean has no values if has no
如果没有，则正确的布尔值没有值
values you know return not has no value
您知道的价值返回没有价值
so basically we're gonna say keep this
所以基本上我们要说保持
filter actually we can even do a filter
过滤器实际上我们甚至可以做一个过滤器
so if it's if it's not null then we keep
所以如果它不为空，那么我们保持
it otherwise don't so we get the result
否则就不行了，所以我们得到了结果
is a stream that we can then collect
是我们可以收集的信息流
collectors that to set put that into a
要设置的收藏家将其放入
set of update
更新集
it's updated right and then that becomes
它被正确更新，然后变成
the thing that we actually keep so
我们实际上保持的东西
here's the updated if you do that right
如果您这样做正确的话，这是更新的
no map has no older values okay let's
没有地图没有较早的值，好吧
see if has no order values then see that
看看是否没有订单值，然后看看
set orders is equal to new hash set
设置订单等于新的哈希集
there we go
我们去
that's much better so now I just
那好多了，所以现在我只是
returned to c return c good so that's
返回到c返回c好，所以
cleaner okay
清洁工还可以
the result of course is now I have an
结果当然是我现在有一个
updated customer set and we could even
更新了客户设置，我们甚至可以
just name it customers that's a little
只是给顾客起个名字而已
dirty but again nobody would you know
肮脏，但又没人会知道
that would hide behind code that nobody
那会藏在没有人的代码后面
else would see and it's still cheaper
其他人会看到，它仍然便宜
than doing an N plus 1 query that kind
比做一个N加1的查询
of thing there there so now empty
那里的东西，所以现在空了
ArrayList
数组列表
okay very very fast now we have a couple
好，非常非常快，现在我们有几个
of different ways to write this data and
写入数据的不同方式
to see the results that's fine and in
看看效果不错
this case there's very less complexity
在这种情况下，复杂度大大降低
right the real meat of the processing is
对，加工的真正肉是
there and this is you know in some cases
在那里，这是你知道的
is actually faster then for example a
实际上比然后更快
handwritten query because it's doing a
手写查询，因为它正在执行
lot of up short compilation that kind of
很多简短的汇编之类的
stuff so it's a you know reasonably
东西，所以这是你合理地知道
efficient it's a when all things are to
有效率的时候
do that to cost benefit analysis they
这样做是为了进行成本效益分析
have to engage in to determine whether
必须参与以确定是否
the practical gains are what the
实际收益是
performance gains I hope you'll err on
性能提升，希望您会继续
the side of activity of course now we
现在当然是活动的一面
have them we have read some data let's
让他们我们读了一些数据让我们
look at look at the look at reading data
看看看数据看
so here I'm going to use it we've read
所以在这里我将使用我们已经阅读的
there let's not look at writing data so
那我们不要看写数据，所以
JDBC template changes in template
模板中的JDBC模板更改
customer service let's do JB Simplot
客服让我们来做JB Simplot
writer there we go
作家，我们去
implements an application runner and
实现应用程序运行程序并
here it's going to be a component or
在这里它将是一个组件或
even better yet a configuration because
甚至更好的配置，因为
we might create some other beans inside
我们可能会在里面创建其他一些beans
it'll be a configuration type
这将是一个配置类型
have an order of what do we say the last
有一个命令，我们怎么说最后一个
one was 3 so this before and it'll have
一个是3，所以在此之前，它将有
a logger alright so there's this and in
一个记录器好吧，这就是
order for us to do this we're going to
为了我们做到这一点，我们要
need to inject the JDBC writer it's a
需要注入JDBC writer，这是一个
private sir jvc template all right
私人先生jvc模板好吧
add the constructor arguments and here
添加构造函数参数，然后在这里
we want to write some data to the
我们想写一些数据到
database I'm going to create a service
我要创建服务的数据库
that we can use to actually write data
我们可以用来实际写入数据
to the database so actually we can we
到数据库，所以实际上我们可以
want to create a service here in so
想在这里创建服务
public static class customer service
公共静态类客户服务
okay and all we're gonna do is we're
好吧，我们要做的就是
gonna read some date to the Davis and
要和戴维斯约会，
prove that it's working so public void
证明它正在工作，所以公共无效
insert string and you know we can even
插入字符串，你知道我们甚至可以
do this directly let's tease of jbz
直接执行此操作，让我们取笑jbz
template directly first jvc template the
模板直接优先jvc模板
constructor arguments and here what
构造函数参数，这里是什么
we'll do is when I say this but JDBC
我会说的是JDBC，
template dot yeah uh not execute right
模板点是啊，执行不正确
well I'll update some data so I want to
好吧，我会更新一些数据，所以我想
update and here we have a number of
更新，这里我们有一些
different overloads but we want to put
不同的重载，但我们想放
access to the generated unique key so we
访问生成的唯一密钥，因此我们
really can only use this third one here
真的只能在这里使用第三个
so we create a new prepared statement
所以我们创建一个新的准备好的语句
creator and then we use a generated key
创建者，然后我们使用生成的密钥
holder all right generated key holder
持有人所有生成的密钥持有人
okay and the key holder we access once
好的，我们只需访问一次密钥持有者
the right has been done so here we're
权利已经完成，所以我们在这里
gonna create the prepared statement
将创建准备好的语句
creator sake on that prepare a statement
创作者的缘故，准备一份声明
insert into customers name email values
插入客户姓名电子邮件值
question mark question mark and I say
问号问号，我说
what I write the statement
我写的声明
and when I get the return when I return
当我回来的时候
the generated keys and then we want to
生成的密钥，然后我们想要
set the premise on that prepared
以准备好的前提为前提
statement so prepared statement is a
声明，所以准备好的声明是
compiled statement that's been compiled
已编译的已编译语句
by the engine by the driver by the
由引擎由驾驶员
sequel server engine you know something
续集服务器引擎，你知道一些
is compiling this so that we don't have
正在编译它，以便我们没有
to so that the engine doesn't have to do
以便引擎不必做
all the syntax tree parsing of the
的所有语法树解析
sequel query right now like as you can
现在就尽可能地进行续集查询
imagine with any compiled language of
用任何一种编译语言来想象
with any language in general there's a
一般而言，任何一种语言都有
preparation phase there's a compilation
准备阶段有一个汇编
phase that looks at the string and turns
看着弦并转动的阶段
it into you know ast is abstract syntax
知道ast是抽象语法
trees and then turns it into op codes
树木，然后将其转化为操作码
and then turns out into bytecode and and
然后变成字节码和
then caches that somewhere right this
然后将其缓存在正确的位置
guy could get disturbed somewhere so
家伙可能会在某个地方被打扰
that they can be easily we've we went to
他们可以很容易地我们去了
memory and in this case it's stored in
内存，在这种情况下，它存储在
the sequel engine so we want to this
续集引擎，所以我们想要这个
statement this here it is is time there
声明这是时候了
all the engine please cache this and you
所有的引擎请缓存它，你
know that way we can just we issue the
知道那样，我们就可以发布
query but only provide new parameters
查询但仅提供新参数
now that we don't have to recompile
现在我们不必重新编译
everything so I'm gonna say prepared
一切，所以我要说准备
statements set string one and then the
语句设置字符串一，然后
first string will be you know the data
您知道数据的第一个字符串
that will run right so again let's just
它将运行正确，所以再次让我们
imagine that we had a you know it's
想象我们有一个你知道的
actually did we actually do that we can
实际上我们确实做到了，我们可以
actually create a service method here
实际上在这里创建服务方法
public void or public customer and we
公众无效或公共客户，我们
want a customer here from let's just do
想要我们这里的客户
this here we'll ignore our orders for
在这里，我们将忽略我们的订单
now
现在
okay there's our customer type and want
好吧，这是我们的客户类型和需求
to have a public void
有公共场合的空虚
sorry public customer insert now I'm
抱歉，现在我要插入公共客户
going to say string name string email
会说字符串名称字符串电子邮件
and we put this all in here and now
我们把这一切放在这里和现在
we've got that generated key holder and
我们已经有了生成的密钥持有人，
we need we have we have it parameters
我们需要我们有它的参数
here so the string the first string is
这里的字符串第一个字符串是
the name right and then the second one
正确的名称，然后是第二个
is the email so there's this and then
是电子邮件，所以有这个，然后
funny we return the prepared statement
好笑，我们返回准备好的声明
so we're creating the prepared statement
所以我们正在创建准备好的语句
creating the parameter setting the
创建参数设置
parameters and then returning it and
参数，然后将其返回
this of course is a nicely written as
这当然写得很好
lambda and what do we have when we do
lambda以及我们做什么时会拥有什么
that well we don't need an actual update
好吧，我们不需要实际更新
call we don't need the this is the
打电话我们不需要这是
number of rows affected we don't
不影响的行数
actually care about that
其实在乎
what we care about is the result of this
我们关心的是这个的结果
generated key holder so we get the key
生成密钥持有人，以便我们获取密钥
which is the number I'm going to turn
这是我要转的号码
that into a long value ID of new
将其转换为新的长值ID
customer and then we can use that to
客户，然后我们可以用它来
look up the record or or do it every one
查找记录，或者每执行一次
right so with the usually you could
对，所以通常
easily just say you know return daviesi
随便说你知道返回戴维西
template query select C dot all from
模板查询全选C点
customers see where see that ID goes
客户看到ID到哪里
question mark and pass that in and then
问号，然后将其传递
of course them the row mapper so new row
当然他们行映射器，所以新的行
mapper of type customer and we have a
客户类型的映射器，我们有一个
heavier
较重
arguments and the arguments are created
参数和参数已创建
for object and the parameters go here is
对于对象和参数去这里是
it the I've never served as the second
我从来没有担任过第二个
one or the third one okay so ID of your
一个或第三个好吧，所以您的ID
customer and you know same ones before
客户和您之前认识相同的人
right same as before so let's don't get
与以前一样正确，所以我们不要
long ID Horace target string name is
长ID Horace目标字符串名称为
that right yep and then artist art gets
是的，然后是艺术家艺术
string email alright so there we go and
字符串电子邮件好了，所以我们去了
that's a lambda nicely done
那是一个很好的lambda
okay so the results is that we can now
好，结果是我们现在可以
make and now um red dates of a base and
现在和现在的红色日期作为基准
get the result back so let's try that
得到结果，所以让我们尝试一下
out in here okay so stream dot of a B
在这里好吧，所以B的流点
see that for each name and we can like
看到每个名字，我们可以喜欢
did it today so I can say insert and log
今天做了，所以我可以说插入并记录
out the result of course insert name
当然要插入名称的结果
name at name.com alright so we'll just
在name.com上命名，好吧，我们只是
when we read this we should see then we
当我们阅读本文时，我们应该看到然后
should see what we should go to get all
应该看到我们应该去得到所有
the data that comes back from the
从中返回的数据
database and say this time JD's template
数据库，然后说这次京东的模板
that query select all from customers and
该查询从客户中选择全部，
you know at this point I've got two of
你知道在这一点上我有两个
these but I'll just reuse it so private
这些，但我会私下重用
real mapper customer
真正的地图绘制者客户
all right good so now there's this
好的，所以现在有了这个
customer role mapper and custom a real
客户角色映射器和自定义真实
mapper that for each log info
每个日志信息的映射器
all right good let's run this and see
好吧，让我们运行它，看看
what we get private final good
我们得到的私人最终利益
ah you can see that right Earl and I did
啊，你可以看到那个伯爵，我做到了
forget something quite important didn't
忘记一些很重要的东西
I forgot the string utils line all right
我忘了字符串utils行
there we go so they there those are
我们去那里，所以他们在那里
there we are our our existing six right
那里是我们现有的六个权利
there in no particular order it seems
似乎没有特别的顺序
I'm seated what I have here
我坐在这里
what do we have customer
我们有什么客户
order by ID that's better looks no it's
按ID排序最好看起来不是
not actually what's going on there we
实际上不是那里发生了什么
run the application and we have seven
运行应用程序，我们有七个
eight nine why don't we have seven eight
八九为什么我们没有七八
nine twice oh because I'm printing out
九次两次哦，因为我正在打印
the inserts right so here I'm logging in
插入正确，所以我在这里登录
the inserts we don't need to do that
插入，我们不需要这样做
let's just get rid of that all right so
让我们摆脱它吧
we know the insert we know that it
我们知道插入物，我们知道它
worked oh we there we go so there's the
工作了哦，我们去了那里，所以
the nine that we expect just the nine
我们期望的九个
and if I restore that code that we had
如果我恢复了我们拥有的代码
before you can see that I was able to
在您看到我能够
get access to the newly generated key
访问新生成的密钥
the key that was generated from the
从生成的密钥
other one commit column there as well so
还有一个提交列
you know we could say a blog that info
你知道我们可以说一个博客
results whatever okay now there you go
结果无论如何现在你去
seven eight nine these are the newly
七八九这些是新
generated IDs all right so that's
生成的ID可以，所以
working good so now that's a very simple
工作很好，所以现在这很简单
example of using an insert so we're
使用插入的示例
doing you know all the sub stuff around
你知道周围所有的子东西吗
generating the results and confirming
生成结果并确认
what we gotten you know you've seen that
我们得到的你知道你已经看到了
before right very simple example using
在正确的非常简单的示例之前使用
the JTP template now the JDBC template
JTP模板现在是JDBC模板
is a like I said it has a nice way to
就像我说的，它有一个很好的方法
write data but it's very much this whole
写入数据，但整个过程非常重要
API is centric around jb's template and
API以jb的模板为中心，并且
you have to remember this recipe right
你要记住这个食谱吧
this whole all of this all that this
所有这一切
whole recipe for using the JDBC time but
使用JDBC时间的整个方法，但是
you have to repeat it each time you want
您每次都要重复一次
to achieve the same thing with the JDBC
用JDBC实现相同的目的
template it's nice to be able to wrap
模板很不错，可以包装
the stuff inside of an object and then
对象内部的东西，然后
be able to repurpose that because most
能够重新利用它，因为大多数
people don't to have to remember all of
人们不必记住所有
the different little things I had to do
我要做的不同的小事情
here to get this to work there's one
在这里让它工作有一个
build to instantiate something or call
建立实例化或调用
something and and get your your game at
东西，让你的游戏在
that current they get the data back that
当前他们将数据取回
you are advertising is available and so
您正在投放广告，因此
for this spring has a slightly different
这个春天有一点不同
approach there's actually two different
方法实际上有两个不同
hierarchies if you are choosing a
层次结构，如果您选择一个
approaches to two right
接近两个权利
using the using spring framework and the
使用using Spring Framework 和
second strategy is around objects so
第二种策略是围绕物体
we've been using the JDBC template which
我们一直在使用JDBC模板
is in the which is in the spring
在春天
framework JBC core package that's hard
框架JBC核心软件包，很难
JDBC package let's see is it core
JDBC包让我们看看它是核心
Oh what Dave's template go it's here in
噢，戴夫的模版在这里
jbz core right but there is a whole
jbz核心权利，但有一个整体
other package called object and that
其他包称为对象和那个
other package lives here and here you
其他包裹住在这里和这里
can see those wrappers around operations
可以看到操作周围的包装器
like query update so procedure sequel
像查询更新一样，所以程序续集
calls sequel functions sequel queries
调用续集函数续集查询
etc and these are basically you create
等，这些基本上是您创建的
objects that wrap the the incantation
包裹咒语的物体
that you're trying to do the operation
您正在尝试执行操作
that you're trying to do and so you can
您正在尝试做的事情，所以您可以
create even factory these different
创建甚至这些不同的工厂
objects and then reuse them so let's do
对象，然后重用它们，让我们开始吧
that now okay so instead of doing this
现在可以了，所以不用这样做
let's just copy the skeleton of our
让我们只复制我们的骨架
previous example here by the way are we
前面的例子是
still in four that's four okay now five
仍然是四个，现在是四个，现在五个
and here this is going to be using T the
这将使用T
object jvc object writer okay good paste
对象jvc对象编写器好粘贴
that in there and everything else kind
在那里，还有其他一切
of the same except for the insert okay
除了插入还可以
and the Creator that we're going to read
还有我们要阅读的创作者
and redo the query as well just to
并重做查询
demonstrate two different ways of
展示两种不同的方式
achieving the same thing here so that's
在这里实现相同的目的
some revisit all that in a second
一些在一秒钟内重新审视
alright so now we've got the insert we
好了，现在我们有了插入
need a query okay so the insert we're
需要一个查询好，所以我们插入
going to achieve using a simple JDBC
使用简单的JDBC来实现
insert and that's an object that's
插入，这是一个对象
actually a thing that we need to to
实际上是我们需要做的事情
manage right so we can create it so
管理正确，这样我们就可以创建它
private final simple JDBC inserts
私有最终简单JDBC插入
it's going to require data sources in it
它将需要数据源
so I'm going to need this I'm going to
所以我需要这个，我要
say simple JDBC insert equals new simple
说简单的JDBC插入等于新的简单
JDBC insert GBC template data source or
JDBC插入GBC模板数据源或
we could just check to the data source
我们可以检查数据源
itself which table name is customers and
本身的表名是客户，
we want to use generated key columns and
我们要使用生成的键列和
the generate key column is going to be
生成键列将是
called ID all right no way to store a
叫ID没办法存储一个
reference to this for we use letter
我们使用信引用此
that's the note that's the nice thing
那是笔记，那是一件好事
about this is that we can reuse these
关于这一点，我们可以重用这些
references right that's the these are
引用权就是这些
meant to be persistent and reused over
旨在保持持久性并在
time so got that got that good now we
时间这么好，现在好了，我们
addressed the sequel operations and the
解决了续集操作和
sequel operation is fairly
续集操作相当
straightforward actually it's really
很简单，实际上
straightforward so we could have map
简单易懂，所以我们可以有地图
containing the string and the object
包含字符串和对象
params equals new hash map name name and
参数等于新的哈希映射名称name和
I always with Java 10 fixes that that
我一直在用Java 10修复该问题
can actually there's a builder for maps
实际上可以有一个地图构建器
and other things but in the meantime I'm
和其他东西，但与此同时我
back in the past so name name email
追溯过去，所以将姓名命名为电子邮件
email and he's met the keys are the
电子邮件，他遇到了关键是
names of the columns in the sequel table
续表中列的名称
all right and so what I'm going to do is
好的，所以我要做的是
I'm going to use the insert operation
我将使用插入操作
this got simple JDBC to insert I'm going
这有简单的JDBC插入我要
to say execute and return key using
说使用执行并返回键
these parameters and the result is the
这些参数，结果是
ID right so we can say long ID equals
ID正确，所以我们可以说长ID等于
the long value and the result of that is
长值及其结果是
what we're gonna return you know we're
我们要回报的是你知道我们
gonna use that to return the customer
用它来回报顾客
now let's talk about getting that
现在让我们谈谈获得
customer let's talk about that now so
客户让我们现在谈谈
we're going to use now a different way
我们现在将以另一种方式使用
that's we know we can come back to this
那就是我们知道我们可以回到这个
a second I suppose we're gonna get a
一秒钟我想我们会得到一个
we're gonna retrieve the customer
我们要去找顾客
amazing a sequel a mapping sequel query
惊人的续集映射续集查询
okay we're going to create a generic
好吧，我们将要创建一个通用的
we're gonna sub class mapping sequel
我们要子类映射的续集
query to parameterize only the thing
查询以仅将事物参数化
that matter to us we're gonna we have to
对我们而言，我们必须
use cases here where we want to get all
我们想要获得全部用例的用例
the records want to get one by ID and
记录要通过ID获得一个
when I get all the records after this
当我得到所有记录之后
like as we did before right to do all so
就像我们在正确做所有事情之前所做的一样
we locate that subclass and that will
我们找到该子类，这将
allow us to to do that easily so private
允许我们轻松地做到这一点，如此私密
static class customer mapping sequel
静态类客户映射续集
query implements the mapping sequel
查询实现映射续集
query from spring not from the simple
从Spring查询而不是从简单查询
flat mapper gonna map to a customer and
平面映射器将映射到客户，并且
in order to do this work we need to you
为了完成这项工作，我们需要您
know that is before new customer RS get
知道那是在新客户RS得到之前
long it's ID honestech is the strings
只要它的ID诚实是字符串
name is to get strength email and that's
名称是为了获得强度电子邮件，那就是
it I suppose okay that's the first bit
我想那是第一位
that we care about extends rather first
我们关心的首先扩展
bit that the camera is that but we have
有点相机，但是我们有
to also configure the datasource a
还配置数据源
sequel statement and some sequel primer
续集声明和一些续集入门
so I'm gonna create a constructor that
所以我要创建一个构造器
has all these things that we care about
有我们关心的所有这些东西
okay so datasource TS string sequel and
好的，所以数据源TS字符串续集和
sequel parameters params alright so it's
续集参数参数没关系，所以
set data source equals datasource sit
设置数据源等于数据源坐
sequel sequel sit parameters is equal to
续集续集坐姿参数等于
params and we need to declare the
参数，我们需要声明
parameters there you go
参数在那里
so for actually you know what it looks
所以实际上您知道它的外观
if I said set parameters but actual
如果我说设置参数但实际
works so something like that and then
像这样工作，然后
funny we need to compile it right and
有趣的是，我们需要正确编译它，
this is actually usually done for you if
实际上，这通常是为您完成的，如果
you call after property set screen will
您在属性设置屏幕后调用
call ft property set if you declare this
如果声明此属性，则调用ft属性集
as a beam right so maybe it's better
作为光束，所以也许更好
just to do that but if you manually
只是这样做，但如果您手动
instantiate instances of this class and
实例化此类的实例，并
you don't then spring manage it you
然后你就不去管理春天了
might forget to call after property set
设置属性后可能会忘记调用
and that would be a mistake it in turn
这反过来又是一个错误
calls compile and you need to do that so
调用编译，您需要这样做
I'm just gonna call this by itself
我要自己叫这个
directly but
直接但是
you know you'll probably you're probably
你知道你可能会
met ''tis as mad as being as in spring
像春天一样疯狂
so with that done now I can create them
这样完成后，我就可以创建它们了
I create instances of them to return
我创建它们的实例以返回
private that's a private final customer
私人的，这是私人的最终客户
mapping sequel quiz all will be a new
映射续集测验都是新的
customer mapping sequel query this will
客户映射续集查询这将
just load all the data so select all
只需加载所有数据，然后全选
from customers and the datasource we're
来自客户和我们的数据源
going to inject as well so I guess we
也要注射，所以我想我们
have to do this in the constructor and
必须在构造函数中执行此操作
by ID this got all equals new customer
通过ID，这等于新客户
mapping sequel query des and select all
映射续集查询des并全选
from customers all right
来自客户的所有权利
and this that by ID equals new customer
而这个ID等于新客户
get data source select all from
获取数据源全选
customers where I'd equals question mark
我等于问号的客户
I'm going to find a new sequel parameter
我要找到一个新的续集参数
here this is a wrapper around the type
这是该类型的包装
the declared type there so we give it a
在那里声明的类型，所以我们给它一个
Java types is it yeah
是Java类型吗
type step into drift and that's our
输入到漂移，这就是我们的
implementation and that's the instance
实现，这就是实例
incident that we need the instance that
我们需要实例的事件
we need and that's it that we can reuse
我们需要的就是可以重复使用的
those now most of the knowledge of
那些现在大多数的知识
calling those queries of running this
调用运行此的那些查询
quiz is now encapsulated in those
测验现在封装在那些
objects those are command objects as
对象是命令对象
well so we're going to stir that up here
好吧，我们要在这里搅拌一下
good and let's reuse that so here we say
好，让我们重用它，所以在这里我们说
this dots by ID dot find object passing
这个点通过ID点找到对象传递
an ID good that was easy and for this we
一件容易的身份证件，为此，我们
say this that all thought executes got
说所有的思想执行
for eat
吃的
long info also very easy and you can
长信息也很容易，您可以
again you can easily see how you could
再次，您可以轻松地看到如何
create you know for things that's
让你知道的东西
slightly different you would probably
可能会略有不同
even create some classes of this that
甚至创建一些这样的类
already had the data sort you know the
已经有了您知道的数据排序
constructor just contained the data
构造函数只包含数据
source and then the sequence statement
源，然后是序列语句
and the parameters were just done for
参数刚刚完成
you automatically right so you'd have a
您会自动对，因此您将拥有
customer mapping sequel that only needed
只需要的客户映射续集
a source you know one for all and one
一生一世
for a particular one for example and
例如一个特定的
forgive it for for queries that are very
原谅非常查询
different you definitely want to just
你肯定只是想与众不同
hide that as much as possible so that
尽可能地隐藏
way you just have objects that you can
您只拥有可以的对象的方式
test easily all right now let's see what
现在轻松测试，让我们看看
happens let's see what we get if we run
发生，让我们看看如果我们跑步会得到什么
this code again alright so again it's
这段代码再次正确，所以再次
logging the data we don't want to do
记录我们不想做的数据
that again but it doesn't it doesn't
再次，但不是，不是
hurt us to show that but it is redundant
伤害我们以证明这一点，但这是多余的
I think let's see if we get rid of this
我想让我们看看是否可以摆脱这种情况
get rid of that extra parenthesis in the
摆脱掉多余的括号
upper one as well
也是上流
already so you can see now we have ABC
已经，所以您现在可以看到我们有ABC
written again that makes sense right
再写一遍，说得对
that's rule writing them again in the
这是规则，再次在
second application runner and that's
第二个应用程序运行者，那就是
working so we can see that the upper
工作，所以我们可以看到
update worked the agenda BC object
更新工作了议程BC对象
writer worked the query work thread the
作者工作查询工作线程
mapping sequel query worked obviously
映射续集查询效果明显
because we wouldn't be able to get this
因为我们无法得到这个
data and the first place to see in the
数据以及在
console Ted didn't work so you know same
控制台Ted无法正常工作，所以您也知道
same result but you notice that we
结果相同，但您注意到我们
didn't actually need the data source I
实际上并不需要我的数据源
used the data source to get reverence to
使用数据源来尊重
the to the data source
到数据源
I use the JB's template rather together
我使用JB的模板，而不是一起使用
to get pointers to the M to the data
获取指向数据的M的指针
source but I could have just injected
来源，但我本来可以注入
that ardently I should have just heard
那我应该早就听到了
you injected that directly right so yeah
你直接注入了，所以是的
that's cleaner all the way much better
一路变得干净多了
alright so there we go much cleaner so
好了，所以我们去了更清洁
this didn't need any of the JB's
这不需要任何JB的
template at all you can encapsulate all
模板，您可以封装所有
that logic in these custom operations if
这些自定义操作中的逻辑
you want operation objects and I I like
你想要操作对象，我喜欢
that style I like this because it's you
我喜欢这种风格，因为是你
know you're encapsulating the business
知道你在封装业务
logic here as much as possible okay no
这里的逻辑尽可能好不
so now what we have is pretty concise
所以现在我们的内容非常简洁
it's still a little bit more tedious
还是有点乏味
than perhaps those who are accustomed to
比那些习惯的人
om software might expect so what we're
om软件可能期望如此，我们
gonna do now is we're going to take this
现在要做的就是我们要接受这个
up one step further and see if we can
再上一步，看看我们能否
get the best balance between an OEM and
在OEM与
our sort of low-level sequel based
我们基于低级的续集
access we're going to use a brand new
访问，我们将使用全新的
protocol spring data JDBC now this is by
协议spring数据JDBC现在由
no means a GA project and I don't want
没什么意思，是GA项目，我不想要
to encourage you all to run out and
鼓励大家用尽
start using it in here and your code
在这里开始使用它，您的代码
right now but that's it it has been
现在，仅此而已
around for a while it's been a it's a
周围已经有一段时间了
project that was a incubated in the
在
community and has been recently brought
社区，最近被带来
into the official spring data umbrella
进入官方 spring data 保护伞
portfolio so we're gonna add this
投资组合，所以我们要添加这个
product to our our our apps are built
我们产品的构建
here we're gonna add this product to our
在这里，我们要将此产品添加到我们的
build the old-fashioned way using some
用一些方法建立老式的方法
dependencies here so
这里的依赖
SD so we need a few things we need the
SD，所以我们需要一些东西
repository in order to use this so we'll
为了使用它，我们将
add this here and then we need the
在这里添加，然后我们需要
version of the dependency we need the
我们需要的依赖版本
dependency itself here
依赖本身
and requisite part of that is that the
必要的部分是
spring data released train itself has to
spring data 发布火车本身不得不
be upgraded so we need to use a snapshot
进行升级，因此我们需要使用快照
or at least a milestone we're just gonna
或至少是一个里程碑
snap track for our purposes we're using
我们正在使用的快速跟踪轨道
spring data lovelace so we're not using
spring data lovelace，所以我们不使用
K anymore not springing out of K but
K不再从K中冒出来，而是
spring that a level is the next release
春天是下一个版本
which hasn't yet been released so here
还没有发布，所以这里
we go Lovelace that'll do
我们去那会做的Lovelace
and with that we can now go ahead and
这样我们就可以继续
build a repository so this is this
建立一个仓库，这就是这个
should be very familiar if you've ever
如果您曾经有过，应该非常熟悉
used spring data before repositories
存储库之前使用的spring数据
just take a object that handles the
只是拿一个处理
tedious you know tedious solonai letting
乏味，你知道乏味的索洛奈
any boring tedious a creation reading
任何无聊乏味的创作阅读
updating and deleting of up data and
更新和删除up数据和
it's going to be a configuration class
这将是一个配置类
that we're going to have to configure
我们将必须配置
first we'll bring in at enable JBC
首先，我们将启用enable JBC
repositories and in here we can do a few
仓库，在这里我们可以做一些
things we load it we're going to create
我们加载的东西我们将要创建
a a application that uses a repository
使用存储库的应用程序
so let's do that
所以我们去做
well create a repository at repository
在存储库中创建一个存储库
interface customer repository extends
界面客户资料库扩展
credit repository here when I have a
当我有一个信用库
custom top-level customer here so I'm
在这里自定义顶级客户
gonna create a customer it'll be this
要创建一个客户，这将是
top level one and they'll have IDs or
最高一级，他们将拥有ID或
private keys of type long and it's just
类型为long的私钥
copy any of these now I could you know I
现在复制其中任何一个，我可以知道吗
want to you know and it's consistent
想要知道并且它是一致的
fashion with everything else else I've
时尚与我所拥有的其他一切
done here I would love to have all this
在这里完成，我很想拥有所有这些
stuff inside of an inter class but
跨班的东西，但
remember this is a bean that spring it's
记得这是春天的 bean
an interface that spring needs to find
春天需要找到的接口
something better than just defined and
比刚刚定义的更好的东西
so because that I keep it at the top
因此，因为我将其保持在顶部
level because it doesn't look for nested
级别，因为它不查找嵌套
interfaces although it does look for
接口，尽管它确实在寻找
nested components right spring will do
正确的弹簧嵌套组件将做
that so we're gonna have this custom
所以我们要有这个习惯
interface there and then custom
界面，然后自定义
repository and customer and and then
存储库和客户，然后
that's it I guess we can actually create
就是这样，我想我们实际上可以创建
a beam of type application runner that
类型应用程序运行器的光束
will use this this data so let's see
将使用此数据，让我们看看
here
这里
class let's could this make this to
上课让我们做这个
configuration make this the JBC the
配置使其成为JBC
application runner all right application
应用程序运行程序所有正确的应用程序
runner and here we'll use the repository
跑步者，这里我们将使用存储库
like so that component now what are we
像这样，该组件现在是什么
gonna do in a visit all the data that
将访问所有的数据
comes back and we can do this a couple
回来，我们可以做几个
ways we can actually let's do a well
我们实际上可以做得好的方法
first what we let's create a custom
首先，我们创建一个自定义
query so let's do a custom query select
查询，让我们进行自定义查询选择
all from customers C where C dot email
全部来自客户C，其中C点电子邮件
equals you know collection of customer
等于您知道客户的集合
find by you know string email all right
找到您知道的字符串电子邮件就可以了
and our customer entity type a customer
并且我们的客户实体输入客户
entity that we're gonna manage through a
我们将通过一个实体来管理的实体
spring data you know look it's just like
你知道的 spring data 就像
that except we're annotating what they
除了我们要注释他们
had to bring data Commons ID annotation
必须带数据共享ID注解
and that's it so let's see now let's go
就是这样，让我们​​现在来看吧
ahead and write them get it to the
提前写给他们去
database here as before copy this and
和以前一样在这里复制数据库并
we're gonna say visit each one of those
我们要说拜访每个
records and this that customer opposed
记录和客户反对的这个
to it save and save a new customer no
保存并保存新客户否
like that alright and then I'll let the
这样好吧，然后我让
log4j bits a logger here I'm gonna say
log4j在这里我要说一个记录器
this customer Pastore that find by email
通过电子邮件找到的该客户Pastore
and it's gonna be you know be at be calm
你一定会保持冷静
and will visit the results
并将访问结果
okay then let's just confirm that
好吧，让我们确认一下
finding everything should work as well
找到一切都应该工作
like so they're cool all right we got it
像这样，他们很酷，我们知道了
so now write the data out now we're
所以现在把数据写出来
gonna have an issue because the table
会有问题，因为桌子
doesn't match right so table see I'm a
匹配不正确，所以表看到我是
customer which is derived by the name of
以名称命名的客户
the type doesn't match anything in the
该类型与
database so we need to customize the
数据库，因此我们需要自定义
naming strategy and here we can do that
命名策略，在这里我们可以做到
in the configuration like so naming
在这样命名的配置中
strategy and we can just return to the
战略，我们可以回到
fourth one save for one method which
第四种节省一种方法
will override get table name okay I'm
会覆盖获取表名，好的
gonna say type dot get simple name drop
会说点号得到简单的名字下降
to lowercase so fix it with s and return
小写，所以用s修复并返回
this like a semicolon okay now what's
这就像分号一样，现在是什么
happening we need to provide the method
发生了，我们需要提供方法
name outside the primer name for a
在引物名称之外的名称
custom repository query fair enough so a
自定义存储库查询足够公平，因此
plan email I think if we had done
计划电子邮件，我想我们是否已完成
question mark and just omitted this it
问号，只是省略了它
will worked as well based on positional
根据位置，效果也会很好
proud you know positioning primer primer
自豪您知道定位底漆底漆
your positioning but um it's fine okay
您的位置，但是很好
so there we go there's our result what
所以我们去那里，我们的结果是什么
do we say we want to look for and then I
我们说我们要寻找，然后我
give this to write this is gonna be
给这个写这将是
order what is it I don't know let's just
点什么，我不知道，让我们
say not seven I think it's seven five
说不是七，我认为是七点五
to skip one let's do six okay already
跳过一个，让我们做六个就可以了
what do we got so the last one is B
我们得到了什么，所以最后一个是B
right
对
find by email oh yeah that's true cuz
通过电子邮件找到哦，是的，真的
we've inserted later let's just try
我们稍后插入，让我们尝试
doing a unique one we've inserted three
做一个独特的，我们插入了三个
different ones in the course of this
在此过程中不同的
program but just to be sure save new
程序，但只是要确保保存新
customer null
客户空
foo bar all right there we go so wait
foo bar好吧，我们去吧，等等
now fit up for foo or a brother bar you
现在适合foo或兄弟酒吧
should get one record back hey hey look
应该得到一个记录回来嘿嘿看
at that
在那个
okay so they left that's a custom crave
好的，所以他们离开了，这是自定义的渴望
using spring data JDBC we still get full
使用spring数据JDBC，我们仍然可以吃饱
control of the quays I wonder if this
控制码头，我想知道这是否
works I wonder if it's smart enough to
我不知道它是否足够聪明
them and further query as it does with
他们，并进一步查询与
other spring data modules so let's
其他spring数据模块，让我们
remove the coil together and see if it
一起拆下线圈，看看是否
if you figures it out based on the name
如果您根据名称算出
of the method which is what a lot of the
该方法的很多
other spring data modules will do for
其他spring数据模块将用于
you and guess not no creases yeah okay
你，你猜不是没有折痕
that's fine we can we don't want to give
很好，我们可以不想给
up quiz when we move to this nice you
当我们移到这个很好的你时，开始测验
know paradigm of using queries so I'm
知道使用查询的范例，所以我
good we now have looked at a number of
好，我们现在看了一些
different ways to use the low level
使用低级别的不同方法
support in spring for JDBC access and
在春季支持JDBC访问和
again this I think makes a fine
再次，我认为这很好
alternatives particularly spring guide
替代品，特别是弹簧导引
GBC particularly things like simple flat
GBC尤其是简单的平板之类的东西
map but I think when you start to use
地图，但我认为当您开始使用时
this main level JDBC sees JDBC support
此主要级别的JDBC看到了JDBC支持
in spring along with the the the JDBC
在春季以及JDBC
template and projects like spring data
模板和项目，例如spring数据
JDBC you get a lot of your business you
通过JDBC，您可以开展很多业务
get a lot of speed you get a lot of the
得到很多速度，你得到很多
things that we want out of a data access
我们想要从数据访问中获取的东西
technology without being encumbered with
技术而不受束缚
a lot of code I have written three
我写了很多代码
hundred sixty three lines of code but
一百六十三行代码，但是
again I've done six different versions
我又做了六个不同的版本
of the same program right and it's still
相同的程序，它仍然
only three and sixty three lines of code
只有三和六十三行代码
you know it doesn't get much simpler
你知道这并没有变得更简单
than that I want to thank you for your
比我要感谢你的
time and hope you got something endless
时间，希望你得到了无尽的东西
and as usual we'll see you next time
和往常一样，我们下次见
you
您